The 11+ — England's grammar-school entrance exam
Top prep usually means costly 1:1 tutoring
ApexMaths — AI-powered 11+ maths, for every family
Skill Builder — adaptive engine
Targets weakest topics · ~75% difficulty (ZPD)
"Show me how" — streaming AI tutor (never reveals the answer)
Instant score + per-question AI review
Live analytics: mastery, accuracy, focus areas
AI writes a plain-English summary for the parent
Cognito · Stripe · Admin — all server-side on Vercel
Vercel ↔ AWS via OIDC federation — no static keys
Vercel env: AWS_ROLE_ARN + AURORA_CLUSTER_ARN
IAM trust policy = the Vercel OIDC identity
Same ARN in Vercel & AWS console ✓
Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL Serverless v2
Why, not which — DynamoDB: KV at scale · DSQL: global writes · Aurora: relational
Relational core: joins · aggregates · transactions · 10 foreign keys
Window functions — computed live, in-engine
RDS Data API over HTTPS — no pool · no VPC · no password
New idea? No. New approach? Yes.
Adaptive tutor · AI review · self-explaining analytics
Effort & potential — not postcode
Built solo · ApexMaths